toptenwholesale.com 2010-03-15

# JP Communications Privacy Policy

  * Home
  * About TopTen
  * Press Center
  * Contact Us
  * **Privacy Policy**
  * Previous Privacy Policies:  
Prior to 9/26/2005
  * Terms Of Use
  * Advertising Program Terms

| 

JP Communications considers your privacy to be very important. We follow the privacy principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement, and are registered with the U.S. Department of Commerce's safe harbor program.

This policy applies to all of our Websites and the services offered by JP Communications (capitalized terms are defined here). For additional information about our privacy policy, please contact us through this or the other Websites or at 970 Los Vallecitos Blvd., Suite 222, San Marcos, California 92069.

This privacy policy covers information we collect and how we use it, choices that you have for your personal information and sharing and transferring of information.

## Information We Collect:

We offer a number of services that do not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us, such as searches of our advertisers database and accessing information, forums and articles on the Websites. For other services, such as posting to the forums or the free classified and for setting up an advertising account, we may collect the following types of information:

  * Member Information \- When you become a Member of TopTenWholesale, WholeSaleU, Wholezilla or our other Websites, we ask you for personal information such as your name, email address, your firms address, a user ID and an account password. We may provide Member Information to companies or individuals who may wish to contact you to offer their goods or services.

  * Personal Information \- Personal Information includes Member Information. In addition, for our advertising programs, we also require credit card or other payment account information. We maintain credit card and other payment account information in encrypted form on secure servers. We do not provide credit card information, your user ID or any password to anyone outside of JP Communications.

  * Cookies \- When you visit one of our Websites we send one or more Cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you do, however, some features and services may not function properly.

  * Server logs \- When you visit one of our Websites our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These Server Logs may include information such as your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your visit and the identity of any cookies that were sent to your browser.

  * User communications - When you send email or other communication to JP Communications, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

  * Newsletter requests - When you join one of our mailing lists you provide us with Personal Information such as your name and email address. We use this information to deliver newsletters to you.

  * Affiliated sites - We offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to JP Communications in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.

  * Links - JP Communications may gather information about which links have been followed on our Websites. For more information about links, URLs and information embedded in Links, please see our Definitions.

  * Other sites - This privacy policy applies to web sites and services that are owned and operated by JP Communications. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

## How We Use Information We Collect:

JP Communications only processes personal information for the purposes described in this privacy policy. In addition to the above, such purposes include:

  * Providing our products and services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising.

  * Auditing and conducting research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services.

  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our Websites, and Developing new services.

JP Communications processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America. We may process personal information to deliver the services that we provide and, in some cases, we may process Personal Information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners.

## Choices For Personal Information:

When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than stated in this Privacy Policy or for the purpose for which it was collected, we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this privacy policy we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use Sensitive Personal Information, unless you have voluntarily posted such information, which we do not recommend.

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services. In that case, however, JP Communications may not be able to provide those services to you.

## Information Sharing:

JP Communications only shares Personal Information with other companies or individuals outside of JP Communications in the following limited circumstances:

  * We may provide Member Information, such as your email address, to companies or individuals who may wish to contact you to offer their goods or services. We do not provide credit card information, your user ID or any password to anyone outside of JP Communications.

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.

  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing Personal Information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this privacy policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation or Valid Legal Process (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, ? detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of JP Communications, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If JP Communications becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We may share with third parties certain pieces of Aggregated, Non-personal Information, such as the number of users who clicked on a particular advertisers link or searched for a particular term, for example. Such information does not identify you individually.

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our customers to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year.

Please contact us at the address below for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data.

## Information Security:

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to Personal Information to JP Communications employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

## Data Integrity:

JP Communications processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this privacy. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

## Accessing And Updating Personal Information:

When you use JP Communications services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information that they want to access, correct or remove before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that we cannot authenticate, would jeopardize the privacy of others, would require us to access information that is not readily accessible or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

## Enforcement:

JP Communications regularly reviews its compliance with this privacy policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy or JP Communications's treatment of personal information by contacting us through this or our other Websites or by writing to us at 970 Los Vallecitos Blvd., Suite 222, San Marcos, California 92069 USA. When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is JP Communications's policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between JP Communications and an individual.

## Changes To This Policy:

Please note that this privacy policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

For additional information about the Websites, JP Communications or our Privacy Policy, please contact us through this or the other Websites or at 970 Los Vallecitos Blvd., Suite 222, San Marcos, California 92069.

## JP Communications Privacy Definitions:

  1. **Personal information** is information that you provide that identifies you. Personal information includes Member Information, such as your name, email address and your firms name, as well as credit card information.

  2. **Member Account** means the account that you created on any of the Websites in order to advertise or to use certain services. You can edit or terminate your Member Account at any time through the Website with which you have the Member Account.

  3. **Member Information** means the information that you provide when signing up for a Member Account at one of our websites. We ask for some Personal Information, such as your name, email address and a physical address, as well as a Username and a password. Member information is used to allow you access to free services, such as classified advertising, and for designing and building advertising campaigns. Member Information allows us to protect you from an unauthorized user of your account. We may share Member Information and Personal Information among our various services in order to customize content and enhance our services for you or with other companies or firms for the purpose of permitting them to contact you to market their goods or services. No account information is shared with anyone other than JP Communications except as specified in the Privacy Policy or with your consent.

You can edit or terminate your Member Account at any time through the Website with which you have the Member Account.

  4. **Websites** means, when used in this Privacy Policy, each of the website properties owned by JP Communications and includes TopTenWholesale.com, WholesaleU, Wholezilla.com and OffPriceNetwork.com.

  5. **Cookie** means a small file sent from JP Communications to your computer that lets our computer identify your computer's browser. We use cookies to remember information about your browser in order to make the Websites easier and more efficient for you to use. You can set your browser so that it does not accept cookies, but you will not be able to use all of the Websites and services as well if you do.

  6. **Server logs** are records that our servers create when you visit our sites. Server Logs include your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your visit and any cookies assigned to your browser.

  7. **Link Information** means information that we receive when a visitor clicks on a link on one of our Websites. JP Communications uses this information to see how visitors use our site and services. We also use this information to count how many times visitors clicked on advertisements in order to know how much to charge the advertiser.

  8. **Sensitive personal information** includes information generally considered to be confidential. Examples include medical information, racial or ethnic origins, age, political or religious beliefs or similar information that is tied to personal information. JP Communications does not collect such information, unless volunteered by you in a public forum, which we highly recommend that you do not do.

  9. **Aggregated non-personal information** means information, including Personal Information and Member Information, about users or Members that is stripped of personally identifiable information and collected into groups that it no longer reflects or references an individually identifiable user. JP Communications may use Aggregated non-personal information to identify user trends and to improve the efficiency and usefulness of the Websites.

  10. **URLs and embedded information** mean the uniform resource locators ("URLs") of web pages that you request by clicking on an advertisers link. When you click through to an advertiser, JP Communications will receive and store the URL of the web sites you visit. The URLs that we receive when you click through to an advertiser does not include any Personal.

For example, when you submit information to a web page (such as a user login ID or registration information), the operator of that web site may "embed" that information - including personal information - into its URL (typically, after a question mark ("?") in the URL). When the URL is transmitted to JP Communications, our servers automatically store the URL, including any personal information that has been embedded after the question mark. JP Communications does not exercise any control over these web sites or whether they embed personal information into URLs.

  11. **Valid legal process** means the process that the government or a private litigant must follow in order to obtain information from a third party, such as JP Communications, and includes search warrants, court orders, or subpoenas. The laws of the place where you live provide the protections you have against intrusions by the government or individuals into your private affairs. JP Communications will comply with information requests resulting from Valid legal process but will not otherwise give Personal or Member Information to the government or third parties.

For additional information about the Websites, JP Communications or our Privacy Policy, please contact us through this or the other Websites or at 970 Los Vallecitos Blvd., Suite 222, San Marcos, California 92069.
